let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who invented C++?",
    answer: "d) Bjarne Stroustrup",
    options: [
      "a) Dennis Ritchie",
      "b) Ken Thompson",
      "c) Brian Kernighan",
      "d) Bjarne Stroustrup"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is C++?",
    answer: "a) C++ is an object oriented programming language",
    options: [
      "a) C++ is an object oriented programming language",
      "b) C++ is a procedural programming language",
      "c) C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
      "d) C++ is a functional programming language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "An array element is accessed using",
    answer: "D. an index number",
    options: [
      "A. a first-in-first-out approach",
      "B. the dot operator",
      "C. a member name",
      "D. an index number"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
    answer: "d) both // comment or /* comment */",
    options: [
      "a) /* comment */",
      "b) // comment */",
      "c) // comment",
      "d) both // comment or /* comment */"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following user-defined header file extensions used in C++?",
    answer: "c) h",
    options: [
      "a) hg",
      "b) cpp",
      "c) h",
      "d) hf"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
    answer: "a) VAR_1234",
    options: [
      "a) VAR_1234",
      "b) $var_name",
      "c) 7VARNAME",
      "d) 7var_name"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
    answer: "d) Friend constructor",
    options: [
      "a) Default constructor",
      "b) Parameterized constructor",
      "c) Copy constructor",
      "d) Friend constructor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
    answer: "d) Top-down",
    options: [
      "a) Left-right",
      "b) Right-left",
      "c) Bottom-up",
      "d) Top-down"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is virtual inheritance in C++?",
    answer: "d) C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class",
    options: [
      "a) C++ technique to enhance multiple inheritance",
      "b) C++ technique to ensure that a private member of the base class can be accessed somehow",
      "c) C++ technique to avoid multiple inheritances of classes",
      "d) C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about this pointer in C++?",
    answer: "c) this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all non-static functions of a class",
    options: [
      "a) this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all static variables of a class",
      "b) this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all the functions of a class",
      "c) this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all non-static functions of a class",
      "d) this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all static functions of a class"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which allows you to create a derived class that inherits properties from more than one base class?",
    answer: "B. Multiple inheritance",
    options: [
      "A. Multilevel inheritance",
      "B. Multiple inheritance",
      "C. Hybrid Inheritance",
      "D. Hierarchical Inheritance"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which feature in OOP allows reusing code?",
    answer: "B) Inheritance",
    options: [
      "A) Polymorphism",
      "B) Inheritance",
      "C) Encapsulation",
      "D) Data hiding"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "A function that changes the state of the cout object is called a(n)",
    answer: "C. manipulator",
    options: [
      "A. member",
      "B. adjuster",
      "C. manipulator",
      "D. operator"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What does C++ append to the end of a string literal constant?",
    answer: "D. a null character",
    options: [
      "A. a space",
      "B. a number sign (#)",
      "C. an asterisk (*)",
      "D. a null character"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "An array element is accessed using",
    answer: "D. an index number",
    options: [
      "A. a first-in-first-out approach",
      "B. the dot operator",
      "C. a member name",
      "D. an index number"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "To hide a data member from the program, you must declare the data member in the _____ section of the class",
    answer: "D. private",
    options: [
      "A. concealed",
      "B. confidential",
      "C. hidden",
      "D. private"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "External documentation includes",
    answer: "D. All of the above",
    options: [
      "A. a printout of the program's code",
      "B. flowcharts",
      "C. IPO charts",
      "D. All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The function whose prototype is void getData(Item *thing); receives",
    answer: "A. a pointer to a structure",
    options: [
      "A. a pointer to a structure",
      "B. a reference to a structure",
      "C. a copy of a structure",
      "D. nothing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Null character needs a space of",
    answer: "B. one byte",
    options: [
      "A. zero bytes",
      "B. one byte",
      "C. three bytes",
      "D. four bytes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The number of structures than can be declared in a single statement is",
    answer: "D. unlimited",
    options: [
      "A. one",
      "B. two",
      "C. three",
      "D. unlimited"
    ]
  }
];